solarreviews.com 2014-11-23

# Solar power installer reviews, solar company reviews, solar panels reviews

www.solarreviews.com is a website run by Solar Investments, with the head office based in Lakewood, Colorado.  The way our site works is that consumers who are interested in solar power visit our website to get information about solar power and to request quotes from Installers of solar power systems in their local area that are interested in providing a quote to install a solar power system for the consumer.

**Requesting quotes**

In order to request a quote from Installers who have registered on our site, you are required to enter some personal information. In most cases, it is basic contact information (your name, address, phone number and email address) to allow Installers to contact you, view your roof online and arrange to give you a quote. We send the quotation request by email to our partner Installers. They are contractually bound to only use your information to establish contact and respond to your request.

**Data protection**

We take great care in ensuring the security of your personal details. Your information will not be shared with any third parties, other than those Installers we send your quote to. We have both organizational and technical safeguards to protect the security of your personal data whilst it is in our database.

**Further information and contact details**

Users of www.solarreviews.com have the right to see their data and make corrections where necessary. If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, or concerns about your personal data, please feel free to contact us via email at support@solarreviews.com

**Changes**

www.solarreviews.com reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time. We recommend regular review of the privacy policy by users.

**Privacy Policy Pertaining to Installers details**

When installers register on this site they will need to enter some personal information that is covered by privacy legislation as well as some information that is public information. We will only use your private information for the purposes to providing those that request quotes on our website for Quote Zones that you have selected with your contact details. The only other use of this data will be for means of us communicating with you in relation to our provision of services to you.

**Credit Card Details**

When you register as an Installer who wishes to have a premium listing you will need to enter your credit card details into the website. As we charge this card monthly, it is necessary that your credit card details be stored for monthly billing. Please note that we do not store your credit card details (other than the last 4 digits) and instead they are stored by the payment gateway provider (Authorize.net). Your credit card details are only used to debit monthly amounts due under the particular plan you have chosen.
